iccc.org 2011-11-30

# ICCC - Privacy Policy

|  | | |   
---|---|---  
 |   
  
 |   
Privacy Policy

**1\. Introduction**

The Indo-Canada Chamber of Commerce’s payment application (“the Application”) facilitates the online payment of annual membership fees and event registration fees, in addition to facilitating event attendee reservations.  
In the course of using the Application, we may collect Personal Information and we have prepared this policy to inform you about our ongoing commitment to ensure that the Personal Information remains accurate and confidential.  
We may from time to time review and revise our privacy practices and this Privacy Policy. Policy changes will apply to the information collected from the date of the revised Privacy Policy as well as to existing information held by us at the time of the amendment.

**2\. What is Personal Information?**

We consider "Personal Information" to mean any information that is voluntarily provided by the customer including name, address, and contact information.  
Ultimately, the Personal Information you provide to the Application is at your discretion and under your control. Any Personal Information that you provide, we collect.

**3\. Why Do We Collect Personal Information?**

Our concern is to provide a forum for the safe and efficient online transaction. In order to facilitate this service, we may use the Personal Information for the following:  
a) facilitate the transaction;  
b) provide the services provided by the Application;  
c) to operate, maintain and manage the Application;  
d) to fulfil our contractual or legal obligations to third parties with respect to your Personal Information; and  
e) to customize and evaluate our services and the Application to you.

**4\. Consent**

By providing Personal Information on the Application, you agree and consent that we may collect, use and disclose your Personal Information in accordance with this Policy. In addition, where appropriate, specific authorizations or consents may be obtained from time to time. In most cases and subject to legal and contractual restrictions, you are free to refuse or withdraw your consent at any time. It should be noted that the Application can only be used if you provide Personal Information. Consequently, if you choose not to provide us with any required Personal Information, we can not continue to allow you to use and/or have access to the Application.

**5\. When We May Disclose Your Personal Information**

We may disclose your Personal Information to any individual or organization in the following circumstances:  
a) to third parties who are our advisors or service providers;  
b) banking partners and/or financial institutions to facilitate the transaction;  
c) to third parties who are, or may be involved in maintaining, reviewing and developing our business systems, procedures and infrastructure including testing or upgrading our systems and/or the Application;  
d) to third parties in offering joint services to you;  
e) to third parties in assisting us monitor the integrity of the Application; and  
f) to third parties when required by applicable law.  
Where we disclose Personal Information to third parties that perform services on our behalf, we will require those third parties to use such information solely for the purposes of providing services to us and to have appropriate safeguards for the protection of that Personal Information.

**6\. The Accuracy and Retention of Personal Information**

We endeavour to ensure that any Personal Information provided and in our possession is as accurate, current and complete as necessary for the purposes for which we use that information. We keep your Personal Information only as long as it is required for the reasons it was collected. The length of time we retain information varies, depending on its use and the nature of the information. This period may extend beyond the end of your relationship with us but it will be only for so long as it is necessary.

**7\. Protection of Personal Information**

We endeavour to maintain appropriate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to the storage of Personal Information so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure, or modification of Personal Information. We use firewalls and maintain the Personal Information in access-restricted room. Access to the Personal Information is password-restricted.

**8\. Cookies**

In using the Application, you may encounter “cookies”. “Cookies” are files or pieces of information that may be stored in a computer’s hard drive when an individual visits a website. Most Internet browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you do not wish to accept cookies, you can set yours to refuse cookies or to alert you when cookies are being sent. "Session" cookies are temporary bits of information that are erased once a visitor exits its web browser window or otherwise turns its computer off. Session cookies are used to improve navigation on websites and to collect aggregate statistical information. The Application may use session cookies. "Persistent" cookies are more permanent bits of information that are placed on the hard drive of a visitor’s computer and stays there unless it is deleted. Persistent cookies store information on a visitor’s computer for a number of purposes, such as retrieving certain information previously provided (e.g., passwords), helping to determine what areas of the website visitors find most valuable, and customizing the website based on visitor preferences. The Application may use persistent cookies. We have no control over the content of third party web sites that individuals may access through hyperlinks on the Application. We encourage everyone to read the privacy policy of every web site they visit.

**9\. Resolving Your Privacy Concerns**

In the event of questions about: (i) access to your Personal Information; (ii) our collection, use, management or disclosure of Personal Information; or (iii) this Policy; please contact us via e-mail at [**_iccc@iccc.org_**](mailto:iccc@iccc.org).|    

|   
---  

---  
|   
---  
|   
  
| **Mississauga Wednesday, November 9, 2011Business Networking Event** **TORONTO Thursday, November 10, 2011Lisa Raitt on Canada's Economy** **Alberta Saturday, November 12, 2011Annual Gala** **TORONTO Thursday, November 24, 2011Chai with CEO: Patrick D'Souza** **Mississauga Friday, December 2, 2011Holiday Dinner and Dance**  
---|---  
|
